War is hell... but peace is f*#!%!! boring.
Buffalo Soldiers is a drama, comedy, war film directed by Gregor Jordan.
A criminal subculture operates among U.S.
soldiers stationed in West Germany just before the fall of the Berlin wall.
Ray Elwood, played by Joaquin Phoenix.
Colonel Berman, played by Ed Harris.
Sergeant Lee, played by Scott Glenn.
Robyn Lee, played by Anna Paquin.
Mrs. Berman, played by Elizabeth McGovern.
Garcia, played by Michael Peña.
Buffalo Soldiers were United States Army regiments composed exclusively of Black American
soldiers, formed during the 19th century to serve on the American frontier.
On September 21, 1866, the 10th Cavalry Regiment was
formed at Fort Leavenworth, Kansas.
According to legend, during the exodus of the 1870s, more than
20,000 African Americans migrated to Kansas.
They hoped their journey would take them far away from poverty from the South.
Others escaped by being soldiers.
They served in the segregated army units and fought in
the Western Indian Wars from 1867 to 1896.
According to legend, the men were called "buffalo
soldiers" by the Apache and Cheyenne.
The soldiers adopted the name as a sign of honor and respect.
Units of Buffalo Soldiers answered the nation's call to arms mainly in the
West, however, also in Cuba, the Philippines, Hawaii, and Mexico.
They had a huge impact on the Reconstruction era.
Although numerous Black Union Army regiments were raised during the Civil War (referred to collectively as the United States Colored
Troops), "Buffalo Soldiers" were established by the U.S Congress as the first all-black Army regiments in peacetime.
The regiments were racially segregated, as the U.S.
military would not desegregate until 1948.
On November 15, 2024, Robert Dixon, the last
surviving Buffalo Soldier, died aged 103.
The oldest Buffalo Soldier, Mark Matthews, died in 2005 at the age of
111 and was buried at Arlington National Cemetery.
The film explores themes of army, corruption, based on
novel or book, germany, berlin wall.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and dark.